citipricerewind.com 2015-03-29

# Privacy - Citi Price Rewind

## Privacy at Citi

Our goal is to maintain your trust and confidence when handling personal information about you.

## You Have Choices

As a Citi customer, you have the opportunity to make choices about how personal information about you may be shared and used. As you consider this, we encourage you to make choices that enable us to provide you with quality products and services that help you meet your financial needs and objectives.

## Security of Personal Information

The security of personal information about you is our priority.

We protect this information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet applicable law. We train our employees in the proper handling of personal information. When we use other companies to provide services for us, we require them to protect the confidentiality of personal information they receive.

## Our Privacy Notice

At account opening, and each year, we send customers an updated copy of Our Privacy Notice that applies to their particular credit card account. To request a copy at any time, call us toll free at the Customer Service number shown on your billing statement or printed on the back of your credit card.

Our Privacy Notice below applies to all consumer accounts and to the following business accounts: CitiBusiness® Cards, Citi® Platinum Select® / AAdvantage® Business Card and oil commercial cards.

## About This Notice

This notice tells you how we collect, handle, and disclose personal information about you and how you can limit this disclosure. It also tells you how you may limit our affiliates from using certain information to market their products or services to you. If you want to limit our disclosing this information, you may call us toll free at the Customer Service number shown on your billing statement or printed on the back of your credit card or send in the Privacy Choices Form that you will receive as part of your paper privacy notice that we provide at account opening and annually to customers. If you are a joint account holder, we will accept instructions from either of you and apply them to the entire account. This notice applies to both current and former customers. We may change this notice from time to time. If we do, we will notify you as required by applicable law.

## Personal Information We Collect and May Disclose

The personal information we collect about you comes from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you, such as your name, address, and telephone number, 
  * Information about your transactions, such as your account balances, payment history, and account activity, and 
  * Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies and other sources, such as your credit bureau report and your credit score.

We may disclose any of the above information that we collect to affiliates and nonaffiliated third parties as described below.

The term "personal information", as used in this notice, means information that identifies you personally. We may use information which does not personally identify you to help manage our businesses and to provide us, our affiliates, and other companies insight into consumer spending behavior. We may do this even if you ask us to limit disclosure of personal information about you, as described in the Privacy Choices Form or call Customer Service to make this election.

## Affiliates to Whom We May Disclose Personal Information

Our affiliates are the family of companies controlled by Citigroup. Affiliates to whom we may disclose personal information about you are in several different businesses, including banking, credit cards, consumer finance, insurance, and securities. Our affiliates include those doing business under the Citi name, such as Citi Cards, Citibank, CitiFinancial and CitiMortgage, as well as others.

## Nonaffiliated Third Parties to Whom We May Disclose Personal Information

Nonaffiliated third parties are those not part of the family of companies controlled by Citigroup.

We may disclose personal information about you to the following types of nonaffiliated third parties: 

  * Financial services providers, such as companies engaged in banking, credit cards, consumer finance, securities, and insurance, and 
  * Non-financial companies, such as companies engaged in direct marketing and the selling of consumer products and services.

If you fill in Box 1 on the Privacy Choices Form, or call Customer Service to make this election, we will not disclose personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties except as follows. First, we may disclose information about you as described above in "Personal Information We Collect and May Disclose" to third parties that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. Second, we may disclose personal information about you to third parties as permitted by law, such as disclosures necessary to process and service your credit card account, to protect against fraud, and to protect the security or confidentiality of our records.

## Your Privacy Choices

This section describes your privacy choices. Please remember that we will continue to protect personal information about you regardless of your privacy choices.

If you are a customer of another Citigroup affiliate, you should also review that privacy notice since you may need to separately notify that affiliate of your privacy choices.

## Limit Disclosure to Nonaffiliated Third Parties (Box 1)

As described in this notice, we will limit the personal information about you that we disclose to nonaffiliated third parties if you fill in Box 1 on the Privacy Choices Form or call Customer Service to make this election.

## Limit Sharing with Citigroup Affiliates (Box 2)

Our ability to share information with our affiliates helps us to more easily provide you with quality products and services to meet your financial needs and goals.

The law allows us to share with our affiliates information about our transactions or experiences with you, such as your account history, and also your name, address, and telephone number. Unless otherwise permitted by law, we will not share with our affiliates other information that you provide to us or that we obtain from third parties (for instance, credit bureaus) if you fill in Box 2 on the Privacy Choices Form or call Customer Service to make this election.

## Limit Marketing by Citigroup Affiliates (Box 3)

Federal law gives you the right to limit some, but not all marketing from our affiliates. You may limit our affiliates from marketing their products and services to you based upon personal information about you that we collect and share with them. This information may include your account history with us and your credit score. If you fill in Box 3 on the Privacy Choices Form or call Customer Service to make this election, we will tell our affiliates to limit their marketing to you based upon this information, unless otherwise permitted by law, such as if you currently do business with one of our affiliates.

## Information for Vermont and California Customers

In response to a Vermont regulation, we will automatically treat accounts with Vermont billing addresses as if you filled in Box 1, Box 2 and Box 3 on the Privacy Choices Form. And if we disclose information about you to nonaffiliated third parties with whom we have joint marketing agreements, we will only disclose your name, address, other contact information, and information about our transactions or experiences with you.

In response to a California law, we will automatically treat accounts with California billing addresses as if you filled in Box 1 on the Privacy Choices Form and will not disclose personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties except as permitted by the applicable California law. We will also limit the sharing of information about you with our affiliates to comply with all California privacy laws that apply to us. To further restrict sharing with and marketing by affiliates as described in this notice, you can fill in Box 2 and Box 3 on the Privacy Choices Form or call Customer Service to make this election.

## Citi Online Privacy Statement

Our Online Privacy Statement describes how we may collect, use and share information you provide when you visit this website, receive our emails or interact with advertisements we have on [third-party websites](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm).

Our Online Privacy Statement does not cover: 

  * Information collected and used on Citi social media sites such as [new.citi.com ](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/newciti.htm)
  * Information collected on [Bundle.com](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/bundle.htm), an affiliate of Citi 
  * Information you provide to the websites we advertise on and may link to

We encourage you to read the privacy policies on these sites. 

  1. What Information Do We Collect? 
  2. How Do We Use the Information We Collect? 
  3. How Do We Use Information From Our Advertisements on Other Websites? 
  4. Can You Control Your Information That's Collected and Used Online? 

## 1\. What Information Do We Collect?

We collect two types of online information: non-personal and personal.

## Non-Personal Information

When you visit our site, we collect the [IP address](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) of the device you use to connect to the Internet. In addition, we gather information such as what browser and which version of it you're using, the type of operating system you have, and which site you came from. This information helps us provide an online experience that matches your device.

When you browse our site or receive one of our emails, Citi and [companies we work with](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm), use [cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) and/or [pixel tags](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) to collect information and store your online preferences.[Cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm)are widely used and most browsers are set up to accept them automatically. If you would prefer, you can choose to [not accept cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm#anchor4).

It's important to note that [cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) and/or [pixel tags](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) do not capture any information that can personally identify you. The information they gather helps us improve your online experience and may include: 

  * Your response to one of our emails 
  * Time and duration of your visit to our site
  * Pages you viewed while on our site

We may also supplement the information we collect with information we receive from other companies. For example, we may use [marketing segments](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) developed by us or other companies to customize certain services to your local area and provide relevant Citi offers tailored to you.

## Personal Information

In addition to the information described in the previous section, we may also gather personal information that you provide to us such as your name, address, phone number, and email.

Collecting this personal information enables us to offer you online experiences that help you with your financial needs. For example, we collect personal information when you are: 

  * Banking online 
  * Applying for a new program or account

If you've enrolled in Citi services, such as online bill payment, we collect personal information about your transactions, and how you interact with third parties such as those you pay like a utility company or phone company. Collecting this information enables us to provide you these services. You can refer to the terms and conditions for your account or service to learn how your information is collected and used.

If we have personal information from you, or information that's publicly available from other sources, we may use it in combination with the information that Citi has collected online. We can use this information to better tailor and personalize our service and marketing communications with you, both online and offline.

The personal information you provide online is held by the Citi business that maintains your account or is processing your application for a new product or service. You can access and/or change information in connection with your account or application by logging on to your account online or telephoning customer service.

Please see the [Privacy Statement](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm#anchor5), which we provide to all our customers, for a comprehensive explanation of how we collect, use and share personal information and what you can do to limit the use and sharing of your information. 

## 2\. How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

Citi uses the information we collect about and from you to manage our business and to offer an enhanced, personalized online experience on our site and [third-party websites](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm).

The information we collect allows us to:

  * Recognize you when you return to our site so we can personalize your experience 
  * Process applications and transactions
  * Respond to your requests 
  * Provide you relevant product and service offers on our site and in other advertising

## 3\. How Do We Use Information from Our Advertisements on Other Websites?

[Companies we work with](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) place and track advertisements on [third-party websites](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm). 

Like most advertisers, we place advertisements where we think they will be most relevant to customers. We place advertisements by developing and using our own [marketing segments](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) that may combine online and offline information about our current and prospective customers. In addition, we may use [marketing segments](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) provided by online publishers and network advertising companies.

Network advertising companies that provide these services have their own privacy policies and are not subject to our Online Privacy Statement. Many of these companies provide ways to [avoid targeted advertising](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm#anchor4) provided by, or thru, them.

## 4\. Can You Control Your Information That's Collected and Used Online?

It's important to note that the information we use about you helps us provide you with products, services and experiences that benefit you. You have the ability to control how your non-personal information is collected and used online.

## Cookies

You can control whether to accept [cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) or not. If you decide to not accept [cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm), some features and services on our site may not work properly because we may not be able to recognize and associate you with your Citi account(s). In addition, the offers we provide when you visit us may not be as relevant to you or tailored to your interests.

If you would prefer not to accept [cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm), you can: 

  * Change your browser settings to notify you when you receive a [cookie](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm), which lets you choose whether or not to accept it 
  * Set your browser to automatically not accept any [cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm)

## Targeted Advertising 

If you prefer to not receive targeted advertising, you can opt out of some network advertising programs that use your information. To do so please visit the [NAI Opt-Out Page](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/opt_out.htm). Please note that even if you choose to remove your information (opt out), you will still see advertisements while you're browsing online. However the advertisements you see may be less relevant to you and your interests.

Additionally, many network advertising programs allow you to view and manage the interest categories they have compiled from your online browsing activities. These interest categories help determine the types of targeted advertisements you may receive. The [NAI Opt-Out Page](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/opt_out.htm) provides a tool that identifies its member companies that have [cookies](http://www.citibank.com/us/cards/privacy.htm) on your browser and provides links to those companies. 

From time to time, we may change this Online Privacy Policy. The effective date of this policy, as stated below, indicates the last time this policy was revised or materially changed. Checking the effective date below allows you to determine whether there have been changes since the last time you reviewed the policy.

This page was last updated on June 6, 2010.

We may change this statement from time to time, so please check periodically.
